(Leonard:)...which they threw intentionally
incomplete to avoid loss of yardage...
(Leonard:)...or to conserve time.
I can't believe they're not penalized
with the loss of a down...
(Leonard:)...and by having to move the line of
scrimmage back to the spot of the foul.
(Penny:)-Here. Have some pizza, sweetie.
-Penny, you know I'm lactose intolerant.
(Penny:)I know.
I just need you to stop talking.
Penny. Penny. Penny.
(Penny:)-Sheldon, come in.
-Thank you.
(Sheldon:)I'd like to make a sandwich,
but I'm out of bread.
(Penny:)-There's some in the fridge.
-You shouldn't keep bread in the fridge.
(Sheldon:)Staleness is caused
by crystallization of the starch...
(Sheldon:)...which occurs faster
at cool temperatures.
On Earth, we say, "Thank you."
(Sheldon:)So, Leonard, how goes the mimesis?
(Sheldon:)-Mimesis?
-You know, mimesis.
(Sheldon:)An action in which the mimic
takes on the properties...